<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Anil Reddy</title>
    <link>https://anil-45.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anil Reddy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:10:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anil-45.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Question Pair Similarity</title>
      <link>https://anil-45.github.io/projects/quesion_pair_similarity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:10:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anil-45.github.io/projects/quesion_pair_similarity/</guid>
      <description>Over 100 million people visit Quora every month, so it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that many people ask similarly worded questions. Multiple questions with the same intent can cause seekers to spend more time finding the best answer to their question, and make writers feel they need to answer multiple versions of the same question. Quora values canonical questions because they provide a better experience to active seekers and writers, and offer more value to both of these groups in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Question Pair Similarity</title>
      <link>https://anil-45.github.io/blogs/question_pair_similarity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:59:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anil-45.github.io/blogs/question_pair_similarity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Over 100 million people visit Quora every month, so it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that many people ask similarly worded questions. Multiple questions with the same intent can cause seekers to spend more time finding the best answer to their question, and make writers feel they need to answer multiple versions of the same question. Quora values canonical questions because they provide a better experience to active seekers and writers, and offer more value to both of these groups in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faulty Wafer Detection</title>
      <link>https://anil-45.github.io/projects/faulty-wafer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:32:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anil-45.github.io/projects/faulty-wafer/</guid>
      <description>In electronics, a wafer (also called a slice or substrate) is a thin slice of semiconductor used for the fabrication of integrated circuits. The goal is to build a machine learning model which predicts whether a wafer needs to be replaced or not (i.e., whether it is working or not) based on the inputs from various sensors. There are two classes: +1 and -1.
+1 means that the wafer is in a working condition and it doesn’t need to be replaced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Crawler</title>
      <link>https://anil-45.github.io/projects/image-crawler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:22:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anil-45.github.io/projects/image-crawler/</guid>
      <description>Multi-threaded tool to download images from the Google search engine based on the objects specified. It helps to scrape the images required for your model building, reducing the manual efforts.
Features You can specify the output directory Runs in both headless and head mode You can specify the number of images to download You can specify the maximum number of google suggestions to use You can specify the maximum workers to use for ThreadPool Screenshots Setup Clone this repo using</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Review Scraper</title>
      <link>https://anil-45.github.io/projects/product-review-scraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 14:22:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anil-45.github.io/projects/product-review-scraper/</guid>
      <description>This project scrapes the reviews of the products from Flipkart and stores them in a database to avoid scraping for the same product at a later point in time.
Features Provides user interface Interactive graphical representation of ratings Screenshots Setup Clone this repo using
git clone https://github.com/Anil-45/ReviewScraper.git Install the required modules using
pip install -r Requirements.txt Usage To use SQL database, generate a config file using generate_config.py.
Open generate_config.py and edit host, username and password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://anil-45.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 12:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anil-45.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an enthusiastic developer with 1.5 years of experience who is passionate about Machine Learning.
Skills Python, C, C++, MySQL, Tensorflow, Linux, Git, Github, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, IoT Experience Associate Projects [Cognizant Technology Solutions] [ Jul 21 - Jan 23] C, C++, Python, Socket Programming, Multi-threading, IoT, Linux, MQTT, QNX, TCU, IVI, Code Quality, Code Coverage ML Intern [Ardberry Technology Private Ltd.] Python, Tensorflow, Heroku, Machine Learning, Deep Learning Performances Animal Breed Classification [2/284] Unlocking City Air Quality [3/271] Data Centric AI Competition 2023 - Image Data [11/106] Allergen Chip Challenge [13/41] DataDrive2030 Early Learning Predictors Challenge [15/311] Forecasting Solar Energy Efficiency [15/227] The Watermark Challenge [23/167] uHack Sentiments 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
